yeah
once upon a time in a land far far away
they lived a beautiful and warm hearted
go one day when her mother passed away
her father remarried another woman
this evil hearted stepmother had two
daughters just as evil as herself her
stepmother and stepsisters treated her
very badly
yeah cannot sit with us on the same
table
you cannot sit with us
the glass fell down Harry and clean it
up Cinderella
well they were out and having fun she
had to stay home and do all the dirty
house work
everybody at home used to call her
Cinderella when she got tired
she said down in front of the fireplace
placed her cat on her lap and try to
warm up with the dying fire
what fine morning they received an
invitation from the palace a big ball is
going to be held at the palace in honor
of the prince and all the girls are
eligible for marriage are invited
while the stepmother was preparing her
daughter's for the ball Cinderella was
unwillingly helping them you have to be
the most beautiful girls in the ball
the Prince must like you why can't I
come all the girls are eligible for
marriage are invited
really it is really a Latino the where
the ball when the day for the ball had
arrived all alone at home
Cinderella couldn't help her too
and started crying right at that moment
a bright light appeared in the children
through the bride light
I feel beautiful
Cinderella could not believe my eyes
because this very was her mother mother
hello my darling I came to help you
you two will go to the ball at the
palace really
but how with my little help
now you go get me the biggest pumpkin
from the garden and you can't hurry up
and fetch me seven mice with one magic
touch the ferry transformed the pumpkin
into a beautiful horse carriage
she then turned her magic 12 the mice
one of the mice became the driver and
the other six turn into beautiful white
horses
now it's your turn
I look like a princess but my there
I do not know how to dance what if the
Prince asks me to with these magic shoes
you will be the best dancing girl at the
bowl
you must have a dance with the prince
oh but don't forget my dear the magic
will be gone by exactly midnight
therefore you have to leave the ball
before the clock it's 12
thank you very much money i will come
before midnight
I promised my mother would I be able to
see you again
I'm always by your side
when Cinderella enter the palace with
her elegance and beauty
suddenly all the heads turn towards her
even her stepsisters could not recognize
her
and of course the handsome prince was
mesmerised by her beauty
the king and the Queen also we're very
fond of Cinderella
now that's what I call a princess it's
Prince immediately asked Cinderella to
dance
Cinderella was floating on the dance
floor thanks to her magic shoes
the stepmother and her daughters were
speechless by her beauty and full of
rage with their jealousy
Cinderella was so happy she could not
feel how fast time had passed and
completely forgot her promise to her
mother suddenly the clock on the wall
caught her eye
it was almost midnight
leading the Prince standing there
she ran down the ballroom stairs and
right when she was running one of her
magic she slipped off her foot
but there was not enough time to turn
around and pick her sure
running after Cinderella the prints
found her shoe lying on the stairs
find the owner of the shoe as soon as
possible if necessary travel the whole
country but finer the men traveled
around the country knocked on every door
and allowed every young girl to try the
shoe on
but the shoe did not hit anyone until
finally they arrived to cinderella's
house both the stepsisters tried the
shoe on
if you push a little further
it will fit yes yes my daughter's feet
are a little swollen caution very tired
but the shoe did not fit either of them
the men said that their captain had seen
another girl inside the house
there's another young lady in the house
as soon as Cinderella put on the shoe
the men knew that it belonged to her
because the shoes fit her fought just
perfectly
you have to come to the palace with this
young lady
our prints are waits for you
the princess men took Cinderella to the
palace
when the prints or Cinderella he
immediately recognized her and was very
happy to see her
he went down on his knees and asked her
to marry me will you marry me
my princess immediately and with great
pleasure
Cinderella accepted the princes proposal
and they lived happily ever after
but so how did it happen that my shoe
didn't lose its magic
I'm always by your side of course mother
it was you all that time